[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sense of the Malayan Tapir, also called Asian Tapir, is underdeveloped?", "correct_answer": "Eyesight", "incorrect_answers": ["Hearing", "Smell", "Touch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What expression is commonly used in Egypt to refer to the annual flooding of the river Nile, the longest river in the world?", "correct_answer": "The Gift of the Nile", "incorrect_answers": ["Feeding of the Soil", "The Blessing of the Nile", "The Mother of Abundance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest island on the planet in terms of territory?", "correct_answer": "Greenland", "incorrect_answers": ["Madagascar", "Sumatra", "New Guinea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the European Unions westernmost point not counting overseas territories?", "correct_answer": "In Portugals Azores islands", "incorrect_answers": ["In Spains Canary islands", "In Iceland", "In Ireland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which popular actor/singer performs the song Beauty School Dropout in the 1978 movie Grease?", "correct_answer": "Frankie Avalon", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony Danza", "Jerry Lee Lewis", "Elvis Presely"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the number of syllables in a haiku (a very short Japanese poetic form).", "correct_answer": "17", "incorrect_answers": ["41", "35", "28"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the foreign exchange student in the classic 80s movie Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Long Duc Dong", "incorrect_answers": ["One Hung Low", "Egg Foo Yeung", "Sum Guy Tony Wang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of a famous guarding monster in Greek Mythology?", "correct_answer": "Cerberus", "incorrect_answers": ["Golem", "Hyde", "Dagon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Prior to 2007, Charlie Chaplin, Alfred Hitchcock, Stanley Kubrick and Martin Scorsese, who directed a total of 13 Top-100 AFI films, shared this one distinction.", "correct_answer": "None of them had won an Oscar for Best Director.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of them had ever made a film that won an Oscar for Best Picture.", "All of them had worked with Lindsay Lohan.", "All of  them had been inspired by Ed Wood."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the missing number in the following sequence:  8, 16, 28, 44, ___, 88, 116, 148, 184.", "correct_answer": "64", "incorrect_answers": ["48", "56", "52"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the movie Lean on Me, Eastside High was built on a cemetery.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Ghost, the main characters are Sam and Molly.  What are their last names?", "correct_answer": "Wheat and Jensen", "incorrect_answers": ["Miller and Jensen", "Brunner and Lopez", "Brown and Smith"]}]